meme4u.com 2016-11-25

# Meme4u.com :: Privacy Policy

### GENERAL MATTERS

#### Overview

Meme4u.com respects our users and protecting our users' privacy and security is a top priority. For this reason, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of our use of your personal information online and your choices regarding that use. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, under what circumstances we disclose it to third-parties, and your rights to update or correct it.

### INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

#### Information Gathered From Our Users And Why?

We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as:

  * The number of unique visitors
  * The frequency with which they visit
  * The areas on the web site that they favor

We only use this type of data in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, helps us to make the product better and better.

### With Whom Dose Meme4u.com Share Information?

We may disclose information to companies that work with us and assist us in providing services to you. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users. 

Meme4u.com reserves the right to work with law enforcement officials in the investigation of any possible unlawful activities of our customers related to electronic communication transmitted on our site. Meme4u.com will have no legal responsibilities for such disclosures. We may also give information to other groups for fraud protection.

### Cookies

We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. For example, cookies allow us to recognize you when you re-enter our web site so that you will not have to sign-in each time you visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on meme4u.com if you choose not to accept cookies, such as Downloads, My Page, address book, favorites, and ecard history. 

### IP Addresses

We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

Meme4u.com INCLUDES THE SENDER IP ADDRESS IN THE HEADER INFORMATION OF EACH ecard NOTIFICATION E-MAIL IT SENDS. IT IS AVAILABLE TO THE ecard RECIPIENT AND ANYONE ELSE WHO IS FORWARDED THE NOTIFICATION E-MAIL. THIS LIMITS YOUR ABILITY TO COMMUNICATE ANONYMOUSLY USING PRODUCTS. OUR PRODUCTS ARE NEITHER INTENDED NOR APPROPRIATE FOR ANONYMOUS COMMUNICATIONS, AND SUCH ACTIVITY IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED BY THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY IN OUR TERMS OF SERVICE. 

### Ecard Messages 

Your e-card messages are always kept confidential and secure.If you send an ecard or any other content from meme4u.com, we collect your e-mail address and your recipient's e-mail address. This information is necessary to send the content and provide confirmation that it has been received. We will not use your recipient's e-mail address for any purpose other than to send the ecard. We may also use your e-mail address to contact you if you have chosen to receive communications from Meme Interactive Pvt. Ltd or meme4u.com. 

### Personalizing Your Experience on the Web Site

We try to personalize your experience on our web sites by tracking ecards and other content you have sent in order to shape our recommendations about the ecards, other products that might be of interest to you. We also examine customer traffic patterns and web site usage to help us enhance the design and layout of the site and make it easier to navigate.

### Newsletters And Alerts

We send to all of our registered users our exclusive Meme4u Newsletter, which alerts you to new features and content. These communications are sent to you directly by AG. We do not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties in connection with the Newsletter. 

You can always decline the Newsletter by un-checking the opt-in box on the "Personalize this ecard" pages or registration pages on our site. 

### USES OF Your PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have provided us your consent, we will use the information we have collected about you in five ways:

  * To send personalized, targeted information that we think our users will find relevant
  * To include targeted advertising within such messages; 
  * To contact the user for feedback and surveys; and
  * To send the user other information about meme4u.com

### Disclosure Exceptions

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third-parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary:

  * To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; 
  * To protect the company's rights and property; 
  * To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages;
  * To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site or The **meme4u.com** service; or 
  * During emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk. 

Your IP address can be accessed by ecard recipients in the header of the notification e-mail. Under certain circumstances, recipients, their legal representatives, or law enforcement authorities may be able to combine this with information disclosed by ISPs to determine the source of a particular communication. By using this service, you knowingly and voluntarily assume any risks associated with such disclosure.

### Editing Your Profile

If you are a member, you have the ability to review and correct your personally identifiable information at any time. Simply click on the "My Page" link at the top of the every page. There, you can change your address information, e-mail type, sign-in, and e-mail permissions. You can revise, add, delete, or completely cancel all Reminder alerts by navigating to the Reminders "my preferences" section from the "Reminders" links found at the top of each page.

### Contests and Promotions

Occasionally, Meme Interactive Pvt Ltd may sponsor contests or promotions on our sites. Participation in such contests is purely voluntary. In order to enter a contest or promotion, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information. By entering, you agree to all of its terms and conditions, which will be clearly outlined in the rules. Where a contest or promotion is not sponsored by Meme Interactive Pvt, the identity of the sponsor will be clearly disclosed in the rules. Meme Interactive Pvt cannot be responsible for actions or policies of third-party contest sponsors. Users are encouraged to review the relevant privacy policy of the sponsor before entering.

### Sale of Assets

In the event that meme4u.com is ever sold, acquired, merged, liquidated, reorganized, or otherwise transferred, we reserve the right to transfer our user databases together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third-party acquiring meme4u.com assets. In the event we do so, we will place a prominent notice of the sale on the homepage of our site, with links to information as to how you can change your privacy preferences.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Meme Interactive Pvt Ltd. will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. When Meme Interactive Pvt Ltd posts changes to this Policy, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of meme4u.com.

While we carefully select the websites we link to, we are not at fault for the privacy practices or content of these websites. You are under the privacy policy of the operator of that site when you give personal information to them, not the meme4u.com privacy policy. Please read the policy of that site before sharing any information.

### USE COMMON SENSE IN ALL YOUR ONLINE ACTIVITIES

Even the best policy can't protect your online privacy and security in all circumstances. Unscrupulous advertisers, hackers, and scam artists are constantly searching the Internet looking for new targets. Your best protection is to understand the limits to privacy on the Internet and use common sense in all of your on-line activities.

Be aware that e-mail is an inherently insecure form of communication. Remember that third parties are sometimes able to illegally intercept your unencrypted messages, including online ecards.

Always monitor your children's on-line activities and educate them as to the rules for safe Internet use.

As always, if you have any questions, please feel free to review our help center where you can contact us with further questions
